One murder is a crime. Two is a mystery.
Maggie Moore(s) is a mystery, comedy film directed by John Slattery.
Bizarre back-to-back murders in an otherwise quiet Arizona desert
town has rattled local Police Chief Jordan Sanders.
The two dead women have no connection to each other –
except they’re both named Maggie Moore.
While unravelling a web of small-town lies and mysteries, the investigation gets even more complicated
when Sanders begins a romantic relationship with one of the murdered women's neighbor, Rita.
Chief Jordan Sanders, played by Jon Hamm.
Rita Grace, played by Tina Fey.
Jay Moore, played by Micah Stock.
Deputy KB Reddy, played by Nick Mohammed.
Kosco, played by Happy Anderson.
Maggie Moore, played by Louisa Krause.
Maggie Moore(s) is a 2023 American black comedy mystery film
directed by John Slattery and written by Paul Bernbaum.
It stars Jon Hamm, Nick Mohammed and Tina Fey.
The film is loosely based on the real life murders of Mary Lou Morris and
Mary McGinnis Morris in October 2000 in Houston, Texas.
The film explores themes of small town, neo-nazism,
arizona, police chief, dark comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.